celtra.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Celtra

### Introduction

Celtra, Inc. (“Celtra,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) respects your privacy, and we take our responsibility of caring for it seriously. This Privacy Policy helps you make informed decisions about your relationship with us, so we encourage you to read it carefully. The information we collect depends on what products or services you use and how you use them. This Privacy Policy applies to visitors of our website located at[ www.celtra.com](http://www.celtra.com/) (the “Website”), who view only publicly-available content (the “Visitors”); users of Celtra’s advertising and creative management platform and related documentation (“Platform Users”) provided through our web sites and applications (the “Celtra Services”), and end users of digital advertisements created and/or trafficked through the Celtra Services (the “End Users”).  By using or accessing our Website or using the Celtra Services (as defined below), you agree to our privacy practices outlined herein. In addition to the practices outlined herein, we adhere to the Interactive Advertising Bureau Europe [Transparency & Consent Framework](http://advertisingconsent.eu/) and are included on the [Global Vendor List](http://advertisingconsent.eu/transparency-consent-framework-global-vendor-list/).

### **We designed this Privacy Policy with these key principles in mind:**

  1. ****To explain important disclosures about the way we use information that you share with us as Visitors, Platform Users, and End Users.
  2. ****To ensure that you understand what information we collect with your permission, and what we do and, most importantly, do not do with that information.
  3. ****To hold us accountable for protecting your rights and your privacy under this policy.

### **Highlights of what you’re consenting to:**

  1. ****The use of cookies and other tracking technologies.
  2. ****The transfer of your information outside of the country where you live.
  3. ****The collection, use, processing and retention of your information by the entities described in this Privacy Policy, including Celtra, as Data Controller (where applicable), as indicated at the bottom of this document.

### **For purposes of this policy:**

**“Personal Data”** for non-residents of the European Economic Area (other than California residents) means any information that can be used to identify, contact, or precisely locate a person, including name, email, address, and telephone number.  

**“Personal Data”** for residents of the European Economic Area means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person; an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural, or social identity of that natural person. This includes IP address and advertising ID (IDFA/AAID).

**“Personal Data”** for residents of California means information that identifies a particular California consumer or household, including, without limitation, name, unique personal identifier, online identifier, geolocation data, professional or employment-related information, or other information as defined in the CCPA.  This includes IP address and advertising ID (IDFA/AAID).

**“Non-Personal Data”** means information not included in the definition of Personal Data, such as pages or ads visited, time spent on pages, browser and device type, and referring and exit pages. For non-residents of the European Economic Area, IP address and advertising IDs (IDFA/AAID) are Non-Personal Data.

## 1\. Information We Collect/Receive and How We Use that Information

In general, there are three categories of information we collect: **(1)** information that we can use to provide additional features and improved experiences if you choose to share that information; **(2)** information that we must have for you to use the Celtra Services; and **(3)** information collected from your interaction with the Celtra Services as an End User of a digital advertisement (hereinafter referred to as “ad” or “ads”).

When you provide Personal Data directly to us, this information is used by Celtra solely for the purposes identified at the point you provide it. Information we collect may be transferred, stored, used, and/or processed as follows:

**I. Contact Information**. When you contact us through the “Contact Us” page on the Website or become a Platform User of the Celtra Services, you will be asked to provide us with certain Personal Data about yourself which may include your name, email address, job title, name of your organization, mailing address, or telephone number.

Consistent with any permissions you may have communicated to us, we may use this information to directly communicate with you for marketing and promotional purposes via emails, notifications, or other messages, and to communicate with you for research purposes including via emails, notifications, or other messages. Platform Users may also receive communications concerning Celtra product updates, training sessions, or events or webinars. If you want to stop receiving such materials from Celtra, you can change your profile settings within the Celtra Services or follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**II. Billing Information**. In certain circumstances, to use the Celtra Services, you may be required to provide additional information which may include a credit card number, expiration date, billing zip code, activation code, and similar information (“Billing Information”).  
Celtra uses this information to process payments. In certain circumstances, Celtra uses third-party service providers to manage credit card processing. These service providers are not permitted to store, retain, or use Billing Information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing.

**III.** **User Activity Data**. In an ongoing effort to improve the Website and the Celtra Services, we automatically collect certain information when Visitors visit the Website and when Platform Users use the Celtra Services (collectively, the “User Activity Data”). This information may include IP address, browser and device type and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, date and time, amount of time spend on pages, what sections of the Website Visitors visit, and other, similar aggregate user data concerning your use of the Website and the Celtra Services.

We may use this data to manage and improve your experience using the Website and the Celtra Services. In some areas of the world, certain User Activity Data may be Personal Data. Where this is the case, we comply with applicable laws regarding our use and processing of Personal Data.  

**IV. Service Data** **.** In connection with providing the Celtra Services and serving ads to End Users, Celtra collects system connection information, such as the incoming IP address for each End User (“Service Data”).  In locations where Service Data constitutes Personal Data, Celtra acts a Data Controller and utilizes this data for legitimate business purposes, including, without limitation, maintaining platform security and availability, fraud detection, and resolving ad serving errors.

**V. Ad Interaction Data**. When End Users interact with ads generated using the Celtra Services, we may collect information on behalf of Celtra’s customers which may be the advertiser, publisher, advertising agency, and/or their agents. Data collected through interaction with the Celtra Services may include time spent viewing an ad, page views, video views, number of ads clicked, IP address, device ID, GPS coordinates, advertising identifiers (IDFA/AAID), Personal Data that you affirmatively elect to share with us through text field forms, and other information about your interaction with the ads (“Ad Interaction Data”).

With respect to Ad Interaction Data, Celtra is acting as a “Data Processor” on behalf of our customers, which may include the advertiser, publisher, and/or their agents who are the Data Controller of your data who may use this information for their lawful advertising purposes to provide you with a more tailored online advertising experience. We may also use the information internally to improve the functionality of the Celtra Services.

**VI. Cookies and similar technologies**.  A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer or device when you visit certain websites.  When we refer to “cookies” we include other technologies with similar purposes. Please refer to Celtra’s [Cookie Policy](https://www.celtra.com/cookie-policy/) for more information on cookies used in connection with the Website.

In connection with the Celtra Service, Celtra and its customers or partners may also use cookies to customize your online advertising experience as an End User based on the preferences or interests known or inferred from the data collected. Celtra customers may use cookies to serve appropriate ads to you and to help track results or measure effectiveness of those ads.  These third-parties may combine information collected in the context of delivering an ad to you with other information they have independently collected over time across different websites, including syncing or connecting behavior across different websites, mobile apps or devices. These third-parties collect and use information under their own privacy policies. To the extent Celtra uses cookies on behalf of a customer in connection with the Celtra Services, Celtra Cookies will persist for no more than ninety (90) days, but may be renewed each time the device is encountered.

## 2\. Sharing and Disclosure of your Personal Data

We may share your information at your direction or as described below at the time of sharing.

**I. Customers**. We share User Activity Data and Ad Interaction Data with our customers who may use this information for their lawful advertising purposes to provide you with a more personalized online advertising experience. We follow customer instructions concerning sharing and disclosing this data, including any applicable terms in our customer agreement or customer’s use of the Services.

**II. Third-Party Service Providers**. Celtra may share your information with Third-Party Service Providers that support us in delivering the Celtra Services to our customers. We may also share your information with companies that help us operate and market the Celtra Services, such as to bill our customers, analyze our Website Visitors, provide customer and technical support, database, analytics, and hosting services, and other operational support. We ensure that such service providers are contractually required to protect your Personal Data at all times.

**III.** **To Comply with the Law**. Celtra may disclose your information to courts, law enforcement or governmental authorities, or authorized third parties, if and to the extent we are required to do so by law, regulation, or legal process.

**IV. Business Transfers**. If Celtra undertakes or is involved in any merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or insolvency event, then we may sell, transfer, or share some or all our assets, including your Personal Data. In this event, we will notify you before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
****

**V. To Enforce Our Rights, Prevent Fraud, and for Safety** **.** Celtra may use Personal Data to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of Celtra or its customers, including enforcing contracts or policies, or in connection with investigating and preventing fraud or security issues.

**VI.** **Corporate Affiliates**.  Celtra may share data with its corporate affiliates, parents,  and/or subsidiaries. 

**VII. Other**. Celtra may also may disclose your information under circumstances not mentioned here with prior consent of the person or third-party that submitted the information to us.

## 3.   Your Choices

**I. Cookies**.  Usually, you can stop your browser from accepting cookies in general or from accepting cookies from a particular website.  All modern browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. You can typically find these settings in the “options” or “preferences” section of your browser.  Please visit our [Cookie Policy](https://www.celtra.com/cookie-policy/) for more information on how to manage your cookie preferences in connection with the Celtra Website.

In some areas of the world, cookies and other identifiers may be Personal Data. Where this is the case, we comply with applicable laws regarding our use and processing of Personal Data. Except in the case of residents of the European Economic Area, by accessing and using our Website, you consent to the use of the cookies and other technologies described above. Residents of the European Economic Area will be able to accept or reject cookies each time they access the site.

**II.  ** **Marketing Communications** **.**  You may choose to sign-up for marketing or other communications from Celtra on the Website.  Should you choose to unsubscribe from any lists for which you registered, you may do so by following the instructions on how to unsubscribe provided in all Celtra communications or by emailing [privacy@celtra.com](mailto:Privacy@celtra.com).  

## 4\. Your Rights & the EU General Data Protection Act **_(_ “GDPR”)**

We are committed to GDPR compliance when enforcement begins on May 25, 2018.  If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, you have the following rights with respect to data for which Celtra is the Data Controller:

  1. The right to request access to, or ask us to provide you with copies of, Personal Data that we hold about you at any time, which may be subject to a fee specified by law for processing your request (but not for making a request for access). If Celtra is the Data Controller with respect to your data, we will respond to your request within a reasonable period, and if Celtra is the Data Processor with respect to your data, we may redirect your request to Celtra’s customer acting as the Data Controller with respect to your data. We may decline a request for access to Personal Data in circumstances prescribed by relevant privacy laws. If we decline a request, we will provide you with a written notice that sets out the reasons for the refusal (unless it would be unreasonable to provide those reasons) and provide you with a statement regarding the mechanisms available to you to make a complaint;
  2. The right to ask us to delete any Personal Data that we hold about you free of charge, unless we are required to maintain a copy of this data pursuant to applicable law;
  3. The right to ask us to update and correct any out-of-date or incorrect or inaccurate Personal Data that we hold about you free of charge. We will take reasonable steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up to date. If we refuse to correct your Personal Data, we will provide you with a written notice that sets out the reasons for our refusal (unless it would be unreasonable to provide those reasons) and provide you with a statement regarding the mechanisms available to you to make a complaint;
  4. The right to opt out of any marketing communications that we (or any third-party to whom we have disclosed your Personal Data with your consent) may send you or to withdraw your prior consent or object to any further processing of your Personal Data;
  5. The right to request information about any automated decisions made using your Personal Data that have legal consequences for you or which significantly affect you; and
  6. The right to lodge a complaint with your local Data Protection Authority concerning Celtra’s processing of your Personal Data.

If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, send us an email at [privacy@celtra.com](mailto:Privacy@Celtra.com) headed “Data Subject Request.” Before we process any request, we may ask you for certain Personal Data to verify your identity, and in situations where Celtra is the Data Processor, consult with the Data Controller of your data. Where permitted by local law, we may reject requests that are unreasonable or impractical. Please allow us a reasonable time to respond to your inquiries and requests.

## 5\. Security of your Personal Data

Celtra uses reasonable technical and organizational security measures to safeguard Personal Data that is submitted to us voluntarily through our Website or the Celtra Services or collected through interactions with the Celtra Services. However, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of third-parties with whom you elect to share your Personal Data and we cannot accept liability for improper access to that data. We cannot guarantee that only authorized persons will view your Personal Data. We cannot ensure that information you share on our website and/or through the Celtra Services will not become publicly available. 

## 6\. Important Notice to All Non-U.S. Residents

Our servers are located in the US. If you are located outside of the US, please be aware that any information provided to us, including Personal Data, will be transferred from your country of origin to the US. Your decision to provide data to us, or to allow us to collect such data through our Website or the Celtra Services, constitutes your consent to this data transfer. If you do not consent to this data transfer, do not submit Personal Data to Celtra.  If you would like Celtra to access, correct, amend, delete, or export any Personal Data that you have shared with Celtra, please email [privacy@celtra.com](mailto:privacy@celtra.com).

## 7\. California Privacy Rights

This section provides additional details about the personal information we collect about California consumers and the rights afforded to them under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”).

For more details about the personal information we have collected over the last 12 months, including the categories of sources, please see the Information We Collect/Receive and How We Use that Information section above. We collect this information for the business and commercial purposes described in this section. We share this information with the categories of third parties described in the Sharing and Disclosure of Your Personal Data section above.  Celtra does not sell (as such term is defined in the CCPA) the personal data we collect (and will not sell it without providing a right to opt out). Please note that we do use third-party cookies for advertising purposes as described in our [Cookie Policy](https://www.celtra.com/cookie-policy/).

Subject to certain limitations, the CCPA provides California consumers the right to request to know more details about the categories or specific pieces of personal information we collect (including how we use and disclose this information), to delete their personal information, to opt out of any “sales” that may be occurring, and to not be discriminated against for exercising these rights.

California consumers may make a request pursuant to their rights under the CCPA by contacting us at [privacy@celtra.com](mailto:privacy@celtra.com) or toll free at 1-833-457-0177.  Celtra will verify your request using the information associated with your account (if any) or any other information you provide to Celtra to facilitate this search.  Government identification may be required. Consumers can also designated an authorized agent to exercise these rights on their behalf.

## 8\. Australia Privacy Rights

If you are an Australian resident, our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your Personal Data will be subject to this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (Privacy Act). Any part of this Privacy Policy that is illegal, unenforceable or inconsistent with the Privacy Act may be severed from this Privacy Policy and the remaining terms or parts of the term of this Privacy Policy will continue in force.

In addition, the following information applies to you:

**I. Anonymity and Pseudonymity** **.** If you are making a general enquiry only, you may deal with us on an anonymous basis or through the use of a pseudonym. However, we will not be able to provide you with any specific information about your Celtra account if you fail to identify yourself to us.

**II. Overseas Disclosure** **.** Personal Data provided to us by Visitors, Platform Users, and End Users in Australia may be disclosed to third party service providers located outside Australia, including in the US, including providers of cloud or other types of networked or electronic storage.

Although these third parties are subject to privacy and confidentiality obligations imposed by contract or the regulatory frameworks of the jurisdiction in which those third parties are located, you acknowledge that:

  * they may not always comply with those obligations, or those obligations may differ from the obligations imposed by privacy and data protection legislation in your jurisdiction; and
  * the third party may be subject to foreign laws which might compel further disclosures of personal information (e.g. to government authorities).

**III.** **Secondary Purpose** **.** You acknowledge that we may use or disclose your Personal Data for a reason other than the reasons set forth in Section 2 (secondary purpose) where the secondary purpose is connected to or associated with a purpose for collection set out in this Privacy Policy, or directly connected to or associated with a purpose for collection if the information is ‘sensitive information’ as that term is defined under the Privacy Act.

**IV**. **Queries, Concerns and Complaints**. If you have any queries, concerns or complaints about the manner in which we have collected, stored, used or disclosed your personal information, please contact the Privacy Officer using the details below:

Privacy Officer:  
Celtra AUS Pty Ltd  
545 Boylston Street, 11th Floor  
Boston, MA 02116  
Email: [Privacy@Celtra.com](mailto:Privacy@Celtra.com)

We will treat your complaint confidentially and, after investigating your complaint, discuss the ways in which we can remedy the situation. We will ensure that we respond to your complaint within a reasonable time (and in any event within the time required by the Privacy Act).

## 9\. Third-Party Social Media Features

Our Website may use social media features, such as “Like” and “Share” buttons, which are operated by third parties such as Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn, Twitter, etc. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Website, and may set a cookie or employ similar technologies to enable the feature to function properly. If you are not logged into your account with the third-party, then the third-party might not know your identity. If you are logged into your account with the third-party, then the third-party might be able to link information about your visit to our Website to your account with them. Similarly, your interactions with these features may be recorded by the third-party. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the third-party providing the feature. Please refer to the respective third-party’s privacy policy to find out more about its data practices, such as what data is collected about you and how the third-party used such data.  

## 10\. Children’s Privacy

The Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. You must be at least 13 years old to use the Website and/or the Celtra Services. We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from any child under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, do not use the Celtra Services and do not provide any Personal Data to us. If you are a parent of a child under 13 years of age and become aware that your child has provided Personal Data to Celtra, please contact us at [privacy@celtra.com](mailto:Privacy@Celtra.com) and you may request access, correction, deletion, and/or objection rights.

## 11\. Links to Other Sites

Our Website and the ads we serve on behalf of customers may, from time to time, contain links to external websites. Celtra encourages you to review the privacy and security policies of any externally linked websites whose information practices may be different from ours. Celtra assumes no responsibility or liability for the information, collection, and disclosure practices of any external websites that a Visitor can access through the Website or the Celtra Services. Please check the privacy policies of these external websites before you submit any Personal Data or other information to them.

## 12\. Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy, our use of cookies, or our policies regarding the collection, use, processing, retention and/or disclosure of your Personal Data, you may contact us as indicated below:

**Data Controller/Processor** :  
Celtra, Inc.  
545 Boylston Street, 11th Floor  
Boston, MA 02116  
Email: [privacy@celtra.com](mailto:Privacy@Celtra.com)

**Privacy Officer** :  
Celtra doo  
Kongresni trg 3  
1000 Ljubljana, Slovenia  
Email: [privacy@celtra.com](mailto:Privacy@Celtra.com)

Toll Free: 1.833.457.0177

**A note to data subjects residing in the European Economic Area** : If you are not satisfied with our response, or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law, data subjects covered under the GDPR framework have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority in the Member State of their habitual residence, place of work, or place of the alleged infringement.

## 13\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may, in our discretion, update this policy from time to time. We’ll notify you of material changes to the Privacy Policy via a notice on our home page ([www.celtra.com)](http://www.celtra.com/). In some cases, we will notify you in advance, and your continued use of the Website and the Celtra Services after Celtra posts a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. We recommend reviewing this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes.

**_Thank you for reading our Privacy Policy!_**
